(Sheldon:)I've extended a friendly,
casual greeting.
(Penny:)Ready to get started?
(Sheldon:)One moment.
(Sheldon:)Subject appears well-rested
and enthusiastic.
(Sheldon:)Apparently, ignorance is bliss.
(Sheldon:)All right, let us begin.
(Sheldon:)-Where's your notebook?
-Um, I don't have one.
How are you gonna take notes
without a notebook?
(Penny:)I have to take notes?
(Sheldon:)How else are you gonna study
for the tests?
(Penny:)-There's gonna be a test?
-Tests.
(Sheldon:)Here. It's college-ruled.
I hope that's not too intimidating.
(Penny:)-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
(Sheldon:)Now, introduction to physics.
(Sheldon:)What is physics?
(Sheldon:)Physics comes
from the ancient Greek word "physika. "